# Abdallah Moussa

Front-End Developer

#### Contact

- 01127124302 01090802294
- Managarah Abdallah.moussa.2017@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/In/abdallah-moussa
- 21<sup>th</sup> street Elgnayen Suez, Egypt
- Abdallah Moussa Portfolio

### Education

-Bachelor's Degree in Computer

Science. (Grade: Good)

Faculty of Computer and Information,

Suez Canal University. (2015-2019)

#### Skills

- HTML5
- CSS, CSS3
- Media Query
- SASS
- Tailwind
- Java Script
- jQuery
- React Js
- Next Js
- PHP/ Laravel
- MySQL
- Problem Solving
- Data Structure & Algorithms

## **Summary**

Innovative Front-End developer with 2 years' experience in web development, loving coding and challenges.

I have a big passion to learn new technologies, I have a good experience in HTML, CSS, JS, modern libraries and frameworks like React Js and Next Js.

I looking forward to have my own technology that compete with current modern technology.

### **Work Experience**

- OCD Digital Services Company (Front End Developer) October 2022 – August 2023.
  - Implement responsive web applications using React.js, tailwind.
- **Freelancing** (Full Stack Developer) January 2022 – Present.
- Work in many large websites, resolve issues and improve performance. Websites... SGS Dass , s4sensors , Xper-erp.. etc.
- ITI Information Technology Institute (Backend internship)

  August 2018 September 2018.

  Docs.
- ITI Information Technology Institute (Frontend internship)

  July 2017 August 2017.

  Docs.
- ITI Information Technology Institute (software engineering internship)

  July 2016 August 2016.

  Docs.

#### **Projects**

x-waiter "for restaurants and cafes management"
 x-waiter is my own project that had sold to many restaurants and cafes.

Libraries...

React.js (front-end), php-laravel (back-end) and MySQL (database)
project website...

xwaiter.com

More Projects on GitHub and Code Pin

Languages Arabic "native" English "good"

Military Service Completed "good idol"